We've all done it. We buy something we think we like and then change our minds about it.
我们都做过这样的事：买下自认为喜欢的东西，之后又改变主意。
Whether panic buying, an impulse purchase or shopper's remorse, we're fortunate many companies allow us to easily exchange or refund items.
无论是恐慌性购买、冲动消费还是购物后悔，幸运的是许多公司允许我们轻松退换或退款。
In fact it's so easy these days that retailers are seeing an increase in a new type of shopper: the serial returner.
事实上，如今退货如此便捷，零售商发现一种新型购物者在增多：习惯性退货者。
A serial returner is someone who buys items, often in bulk, only to return most of them.
习惯性退货者是指购买物品（常为批量购买）后却退回大部分的人。
41-year-old Hester Grainger, founder of Mumala Club, estimates spending £300 to £400 each month on clothes, but returning "around 80%", she told the BBC.
41岁的赫斯特・格兰杰是Mumala Club创始人，她告诉BBC，自己每月估计花300到400英镑买衣服，但会退回“约80%”。
This isn't unique.
这并非个例。
Barclaycard, which processes nearly half of the UK's credit and debit card transactions, says that in the last two years 26% of retailers have seen an increase in in-store and online returns – with the number of items being sent back up by 22%.
处理英国近一半信用卡和借记卡交易的巴克莱卡公司表示，过去两年里，26%的零售商发现线下和线上退货量增加——退回物品数量上升了22%。
It's a problem for companies.
这对企业是个问题。
Handling these returns eats into profits.
处理这些退货会侵蚀利润。
Free delivery for the customer means the company foots the bill.
顾客享受免费配送意味着公司买单。
Items may need to be repackaged. They are damaged - making them unfit for resale.
物品可能需要重新包装，若已损坏则无法再售。
Tony Mannix, CEO of Clipper, a logistics firm that handles returned goods for major retailers, said about 5% of them end up "being binned." Sometimes the fast fashion cycle has moved on.
为大型零售商处理退货的物流公司Clipper的首席执行官托尼・曼尼克斯称，约5%的退货最终“被扔进垃圾桶”。
By the time the item comes back, it becomes a cut-price item on a reduced-to-clear rail - at further loss to the company.
有时快时尚周期已更新，当物品退回时，只能作为清仓打折商品——公司进一步亏损。
Some companies are taking action to deter this behaviour.
一些公司正采取行动遏制这种行为。
According to a BBC article, four in ten retailers now say they charge for returns to discourage the sending of non-faulty items.
BBC一篇文章称，十分之四的零售商表示现在对退货收费，以阻止非瑕疵商品的退回。
Online retail giant Amazon was reported to have started barring customers with too many returned items.
据报道，在线零售巨头亚马逊已开始禁止顾客过多地退货。
This is something a study by retail management system Brightpearl found over half of UK fashion retailers would consider.
零售管理系统Brightpearl的研究发现，超半数英国时尚零售商会考虑这一做法。
And Barclaycard says a third of retailers have hiked their prices to cover these returns.
巴克莱卡公司称，三分之一的零售商已涨价以弥补退货成本。
But Vicky Brock, director of data innovation at ReBound Returns, a returns management software system, believes this isn't the best strategy.
但退货管理软件系统ReBound Returns的数据创新总监维姬・布洛克认为，这并非最佳策略。
Speaking in a BBC article, she says discouraging returns shows a lack of understanding by the retailer.
她在BBC文章中表示，阻止退货表明零售商缺乏同理心。
Using data, companies can reduce returns by helping customers choose better.
利用数据，公司可通过帮助顾客更好地选择来减少退货。
Some companies such as Uniqlo and Asos already provide a suggested size based on the customer's previous purchases and information on height and weight.
优衣库和Asos等公司已根据顾客过往购买记录及身高体重信息提供尺码建议。
Ultimately, she says, returns are now as much a part of the shopping experience as buying things, and shops need to take this into consideration.
她称，从根本上说，退货如今和购物一样是消费体验的一部分，商家需要考虑这一点。